<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CRA - Climate Resilient Agriculture</string>

    <string name="progresstitle">Loading... Please Wait</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="gps_title">GPS is not Enabled!</string>
    <string name="gps_msg">Do you want to turn on GPS?</string>

    <string name="nrm_title">Natural Resource Management</string>
    <string name="nrm_content_line1">It brings together land use planning, water management and bio – diversity conservation.</string>
    <string name="nrm_content_line2">First step for improving the dryland crop yields is the conservation of rainwater. A soil
and water conservation measure varies with the soil type and agro-climatic location and their
effectiveness cannot be generalized. But if available rainwater harvested, maximum extent the
ground water could be recharged and improved the crop status.</string>


    <string name="rain_title">A. Rainwater Harvesting Structures</string>
    <string name="rain_content_line1">Rainwater harvested can be used for recharging groundwater through suitable structures
like recharge trenches (Check dam), recharge pits (Community pond &amp;Farm pond), bore wells
and open wells. Harvested water used for supplementary irrigation of 5-7 cm during the period of
moisture stress at critical growth stages of yield gain in number of dryland crops.</string>
    <string name="rain_sub_title1">Community Pond</string>
    <string name="rain_subcontent_line1">Structures in the community land commonly used to store rainwater. Community pond
collects excess runoff water during monsoon season and recharge borewells and open wells. So
the available community ponds should be renovated and keep ready to capture excess run off
water. If no community pond is available new ponds should be constructed. A 301ft Length ×180
ft Breadth ×15 ft Depth sized pond can capture 22,999 Cu.m of rainwater.</string>
    <string name="rain_sub_title2">Farm pond</string>
    <string name="rain_subcontent_line2">Farm ponds can be created at the farmers’ fields used to collect the rainwater in water
harvesting structures during monsoon season. A (20 ft × 20 ft × 5 ft) sized pond can capture 55
cum rainwater in their field, that assist to recharge their open wells and bore wells. Water
retention was seen from September to November months normally.</string>
    <string name="rain_sub_title3">Check Dam</string>
    <string name="rain_subcontent_line3">Prevent overflow during rainy season which increases the recharge of ground water level.</string>


    <string name="insitu_title">B. Insitu moisture conservation</string>
    <string name="insitu_content_line1">Off season land treatments such as summer ploughing, compartmental bunding,
cultivation across the slope, conservation furrow, mulching, ridges &amp;furrows and micro
catchments are the practices increase the moisture status of the fields.</string>
    <string name="insitu_sub_title1">Summer ploughing</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line1">Summer ploughing is the operation done during the summer months. Breaking of hard
crusted upper layer of the soil and deep ploughing. Tillage improves the soil aeration, increases
the infiltration capacity, permeability of the soil and kills the weeds, insect &amp; disease causing
organisms. Cultivation across the slope helps to retaining 10% more rainwater.</string>
    <string name="insitu_sub_title2">Compartmental bunding</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point1">\u2022 Small compartments act as a dam and store the rainfall received in the
compartments for longer period</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point2">\u2022 Suitable for lesser rainfall areas for effective moisture conservation practices</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point3">\u2022 It retains about 37% additional soil moisture</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point4">\u2022 Increases the water holding capacity of the soil</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point5">\u2022 20 % higher grain yield</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point6">\u2022 Crops did not show any moisture stress / withered condition for 25 days dry spells</string>
    <string name="insitu_sub_title3">Soil health management practice and soil test based fertilizer application</string>
    <string name="insitu_sub_title4">Green Manuring - Multigrain Incorporation</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line2">To improve the fertility status of the soil as well as to overcome the shortage of organic
manures, multigrain green manuring promoted and demonstrated at namakkal from 2016 to till
date. Multigrain green mnuring contains mixture of seed as follows.</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line3"><b>Cereal crops:</b> Rice, Maize, peralmillet, Tenai, Varagu, samai, Kuthiraivali and sorghum</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line4"><b>Pulse crops:</b> Greengram, blackgram, Horse gram, Red gram, Cowpea and Moth bean</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line5"><b>Oil seeds:</b> Groundnut, Sesamum, castor and Sunflower</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line6"><b>Spice crops:</b> Coriander, Cumin and Mustard.</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line7"><b>Green manures:</b> Sunhemp, Danita, Agathi, Calotropics, Neem and Kolinchi</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point7">\u27A3 Take 20 gm of small size seeds</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point8">\u27A3 1 -2 kg for medium size seeds</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_point9">\u27A3 2 – 3 kg for big size seeds</string>
    <string name="insitu_subcontent_line8">By improved practising the above practise within 3 years, increase in Organic carbon was
increased 0.05%, available N was 28 kg and Zinc was 0.09 mg/kg.</string>


    <string name="micro_title">C. Micro irrigation</string>
    <string name="micro_content_line1">To minimize the potential use of water and increases the area of cultivation for all crops.
Micro irrigation systems are drip irrigation, Sprinkler, Raingun and laser spray micro irrigation.</string>


    <string name="manual_title">D. Manual Weather Station</string>
    <string name="manual_content_line1">A weather station is a facility on land with instruments and equipments for measuring
atmospheric conditions to provide information for weather forecasts on weather and climate. The
measurements taken include temperature, rain gauge, humidity, wind speed and wind direction.</string>
    <string name="manual_content_point1">\u2022 Thermometer for measuring air temperature</string>
    <string name="manual_content_point2">\u2022 Rain gauge for measuring liquid precipitation over a set period of time</string>
    <string name="manual_content_point3">\u2022 Hydrometer for measuring humidity</string>
    <string name="manual_content_point4">\u2022 Anemometer for measuring wind speed</string>
    <string name="manual_content_point5">\u2022 Wind vane for measuring wind blowing direction</string>
</resources>